wonderingsound.com 2017-05-18

# Privacy Policy | Wondering Sound

Last updated: 9/30/14

We take your privacy very seriously.  Your Information and Your Data are subject to our “Privacy Policy.”  By using the Website you agree to and consent to the collection and use of Your Information and Your Data by us as described herein.

Some terms used herein are defined in the last paragraph of this Privacy Policy.  Please refer below for definitions.

This Privacy Policy may be amended by us from time to time without notice to you.  You will periodically review the controlling version of this Privacy Policy, and by continuing to use the Website and Service subsequent to our making available an amended version of this Privacy Policy, you thereby acknowledge, agree and consent to such amendment.

We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under 13.  In fact, we do not offer the Website to anyone under the age of 13.  If you are under 13, please do not submit any personal information.

We may collect non-personally identifiable information about you in a number of ways, including tracking your activities through your IP address, computer settings or most-recently visited URL.  We do not collect any personally identifiable information about you unless you voluntarily submit such information to us.  The types of information that may be requested include without limitation your name, email address, Twitter or Facebook usernames or other usernames and aliases used for purposes of linking to and/or posting on your social media accounts.

When you use the Website, we might insert some instructions on your computer, tablet or mobile device.  These instructions will be in the form of a “cookie” or similar file.  Cookies are small pieces of instruction stored on your hard drive or device, not on our Website.  Cookies may help you navigate the Website as easily as possible.  We may use cookies to deliver content specific to your interests.  You can delete these cookies by changing your privacy preferences in your internet browser.

We typically use Your Information and Your Data for the purpose of providing you the Website and Service to offer you additional products and services from us or from others that may be of interest to you, and to improve the design and performance of the Website.  We may share Your Information with third parties to deliver to you certain content, information, services and notices from third parties as well as communications regarding information, events, content, products and services of such third parties.  You may opt out of receiving email communications by clicking “unsubscribe” from an email sent to you by us or any third party.

We may also require you to provide Your Information in order to enter a contest or sweepstakes. We may disclose Your Information to third parties in order to facilitate such contest or sweepstakes. 

We may disclose Your Information, Content and Your Data if, among other things, we are required to do so by law or if acting with a good faith belief that such disclosure is reasonably necessary to: (1) comply with legal process; (2) enforce the TERMS; (3) respond to claims that any Content violates the rights of third parties; (4) respond to your requests for customer service; or (5) protect our rights, property or personal safety, or the rights, property or personal safety of our users or the public.

The Service has physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and help prevent unauthorized access to Your Information and Your Data.  Although we take appropriate measures to safeguard against unauthorized disclosures of Your Information and Your Data, we cannot assure you that Your Information (including your personally identifiable information ) that we collect will never be disclosed in a manner that is inconsistent with this Privacy Policy.

The Service may contain links to other web sites.  We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such web sites.  Third parties may display advertisements on the Service and on such web sites.  These advertisements may contain cookies.  These third parties may collect information or insert cookies without our knowledge.

This Privacy Policy is governed by and incorporated by reference into the TERMS available [here](http://www.wonderingsound.com/terms/), and should be interpreted consistent therewith.  If you believe that we have violated this Privacy Policy, please contact us at legal@emusic.com, or you may pursue binding arbitration pursuant to the TERMS.

This Privacy Policy is governed by and incorporated by reference into the TERMS available [here](http://www.wonderingsound.com/terms/) and should be interpreted consistent therewith.

“Content” refers to Your Information and Your Data, as well as data, or content of any kind, uploaded, posted, made available, shared or transmitted by you or another user to or through the Service.

“we” or “us” or “our” refer to eMusic.com Inc., its successors, assigns, subsidiaries, affiliates, officers, employees, agents, partners and licensors/licensees.

“Website and Service” refer to the content, features and functionality (“Service”) made available to users at the Internet website located at the URL www.wonderingsound.com and its accompanying pages, as well as via email communications, mobile applications and other media now existing or hereafter devised (“Website”).

“Your Information” refers to information submitted to us by you including your name and email address.

“Your Data” refers to data we collect about you through your use of the Website, including your IP address or other non-personally identifiable information.
